Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم الإدارة، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
Where is she?
أين هي؟
It's you?
أنت هو؟
Your Lordship, are you shocked
يا صاحب السعادة، هل أنت مصدوم؟
that the drug you gave me wasn't strong enough?
هل الدواء الذي أعطيتني إياه لم يكن قوياً بما فيه الكفاية؟
Drug?
دواء؟
If you intend to help Li Wan'er,
إذا كنت تنوي مساعدة لي وان إير،
why did you act before me?
لماذا تصرفت قبلي؟
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
The servants of the residence told me that you gave me a box.
أخبرني خدم المنزل أنك أعطيتني صندوقاً.
I passed out after I opened it.
أغمي عليّ بعد أن فتحته.
Then, I was brought here.
ثم أُحضرت إلى هنا.
I never asked my servants to do such a thing.
لم أطلب قط من خدمي أن يفعلوا مثل هذا الشيء.
Regardless of whether you did it or not,
بغض النظر عما إذا كنت قد فعلت ذلك أم لا،
I've let you have a taste of your own medicine
لقد جعلتك تتذوق مرارة أفعالك
and knocked out Li Wan'er.
وأسقط لي وان إير أرضاً.
When is the auction going to start?
متى سيبدأ المزاد؟
What's the rush?
ما الداعي للعجلة؟
It will begin soon.
سيبدأ ذلك قريباً.
I've been waiting for half a day.
لقد انتظرت لنصف يوم.
If I didn't wake up in time,
لو لم أستيقظ في الوقت المناسب،
I would be the one being appraised.
سأكون أنا من يتم تقييمه.
Come back with me.
عد معي.
I'll give you an explanation.
سأقدم لك شرحاً.
=The Architect=
=المهندس المعماري=
=Episode 11= (Come and Take My Life Anytime)
=الحلقة 11= (تعال وخذ حياتي في أي وقت)
I'm sure all of you know the rules.
أنا متأكد من أنكم جميعاً تعرفون القواعد.
The highest bidder wins.
يفوز صاحب أعلى عرض.
(Ugly) Get your money ready.
(قبيح) جهّز نقودك.
We will begin soon.
سنبدأ قريباً.
The auction begins.
يبدأ المزاد.
I bid 2,000 taels!
عرضت ألفي تيل!
2,000 taels!
2000 تايل!
I bid 5,000 taels!
لقد عرضت 5000 تيل!
5,000 taels!
5000 تايل!
Any higher bids?
هل من عروض أسعار أعلى؟
7,000 taels!
7000 تايل!
7,000 taels! Any higher bids?
7000 تيل! هل من عروض أعلى؟
8,000 taels!
8000 تايل!
10,000 taels!
10.000 تايل!
This young master bids 10,000 taels!
هذا السيد الشاب يعرض 10000 تيل!
Any higher bids?
هل من عروض أسعار أعلى؟
12,000 taels!
12000 تايل!
You have good taste, Sir!
ذوقك رفيع يا سيدي!
15,000 taels!
15000 تايل!
20,000 taels!
20.000 تايل!
Tonight's top courtesan
أفضل عاهرة الليلة
belongs to you, Master Liu.
هذا ملكك يا سيد ليو.
If you want to leave,
إذا كنت ترغب في المغادرة،
I will bring you out of this place safely.
سأخرجك من هذا المكان بأمان.
What do you mean, Your Lordship?
ماذا تقصد يا صاحب السمو؟
Is someone going to stop me?
هل سيوقفني أحد؟
Master Liu, you are lucky.
يا سيد ليو، أنت محظوظ.
Congratulations, Official Liu.
تهانينا، أيها المسؤول ليو.
Master Liu,
الأستاذ ليو،
I guarantee it's worth what you paid.
أضمن لك أنها تستحق ما دفعته.
Come.
يأتي.
Raise the curtain
ارفع الستار
and let Master Liu appraise the goods.
وليقم السيد ليو بتقييم البضائع.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
I am the current princess,
أنا الأميرة الحالية،
and the emperor's foster daughter!
وابنة الإمبراطور بالتبني!
How dare you treat me rudely!
كيف تجرؤ على معاملتي بوقاحة!
Seriously?
بجد؟
Princess?
أميرة؟
Calm down, Miss.
اهدئي يا آنسة.
If you serve Master Liu,
إذا خدمتَ السيد ليو،
I'm sure your life
أنا متأكد من أن حياتك
will be better than a princess's.
سيكون أفضل من أميرة.
Just follow Master Liu
ما عليك سوى اتباع المعلم ليو
and you can enjoy all things in life!
ويمكنك الاستمتاع بكل شيء في الحياة!
Isn't it better than your current situation?
أليس هذا أفضل من وضعك الحالي؟
Master Liu is rich!
السيد ليو غني!
Yes!
نعم!
Exactly!
بالضبط!
I will gouge all your eyes
سأفقأ جميع عيونكم
and cut all your tongues!
واقطعوا ألسنتكم جميعاً!
She's a feisty one.
إنها فتاة عنيدة.
How interesting.
مثير للاهتمام.
I like her.
أنا معجب بها.
Pretty,
جميل،
I'm coming for you.
أنا قادم إليك.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
This...
هذا...
Who is this?
من هذا؟
I said
قلت
I'd gouge all your eyes
سأفقأ جميع عيونكم
and cut all your tongues!
واقطعوا ألسنتكم جميعاً!
How can I go back on my word?
كيف لي أن أتراجع عن كلمتي؟
Your Highness!
يا صاحب السمو!
Your Highness, please spare me!
يا صاحب السمو، أرجوك ارحمني!
Your Highness, spare me!
يا صاحب السمو، ارحمني!
If I knew you were the princess,
لو كنت أعرف أنكِ الأميرة،
I'd never do it no matter how brave I am.
لن أفعل ذلك أبداً مهما بلغت شجاعتي.
Your Highness, I beg you.
يا صاحب السمو، أرجوكم.
Spare me.
ارحمني.
Do it!
افعلها!
Your Highness, spare me!
يا صاحب السمو، ارحمني!
You didn't even blink when you tried to harm me.
لم ترمش حتى عندما حاولت إيذائي.
Why are you trying to kill others
لماذا تحاول قتل الآخرين
when you are the one being viewed and appraised now?
عندما تكون أنت الشخص الذي يتم النظر إليه وتقييمه الآن؟
Wretch.
البائس.
Who do you think you are?
من تظن نفسك؟
Not only am I going to kill you today,
لن أكتفي بقتلك اليوم،
but I want everyone here
لكنني أريد أن يكون الجميع هنا
to die with you.
أن أموت معك.
Your Highness, spare me!
يا صاحب السمو، ارحمني!
You've been humiliated
لقد تعرضت للإهانة
yet you still don't hold back.
ومع ذلك، ما زلت لا تتراجع.
You only want to take other people's lives.
أنت لا تريد سوى إزهاق أرواح الآخرين.
Not only does the Princess of Daliang
ليس فقط أميرة داليانغ
not contribute to the kingdom,
عدم المساهمة في المملكة،
but she also wants the people's blood on her hands.
لكنها تريد أيضاً أن تتلطخ يداها بدماء الناس.
How dare you call yourself a member of Daliang's royalty?
كيف تجرؤ على تسمية نفسك أحد أفراد العائلة المالكة في داليانغ؟
Preposterous!
أمرٌ سخيف!
You are just a courtesan in a brothel.
أنتِ مجرد عاهرة في بيت دعارة.
How dare you reprimand me?
كيف تجرؤ على توبيخي؟
Today,
اليوم،
I will cut off all your tongues!
سأقطع ألسنتكم جميعاً!
I want all of you to reincarnate
أتمنى لكم جميعاً أن تتجسدوا من جديد
as mutes.
كأجهزة كتم الصوت.
Li Wan'er.
لي وان إير.
You can kill us,
بإمكانكم قتلنا،
but you can't stop the people from saying what they want.
لكن لا يمكنك منع الناس من قول ما يريدون.
Even if everyone here is dead,
حتى لو كان جميع من هنا أمواتاً،
your evil deeds today
أفعالك الشريرة اليوم
will be spread around the world.
سينتشر في جميع أنحاء العالم.
Kill them!
اقتلهم!
Who dares kill her?
من يجرؤ على قتلها؟
Yu.
يو.
Don't look at me.
لا تنظر إليّ.
When I'm around,
عندما أكون موجوداً،
anyone who acts recklessly
أي شخص يتصرف بتهور
will be punished for the crime of harming the common people.
سيعاقبون على جريمة إلحاق الأذى بالعامة.
Li Wan'er,
لي وان إير،
you are no longer
لم تعد
the princess I know.
الأميرة التي أعرفها.
You came back for them.
لقد عدت من أجلهم.
Aren't you afraid of exposing yourself before Li Wan'er?
ألا تخافين من كشف نفسك أمام لي وان إير؟
No one knows the feeling
لا أحد يعرف هذا الشعور
of being trampled on
من التعرض للدوس
with no right to explain more than I do.
ليس لي الحق في شرح أكثر مما أفعل.
However,
لكن،
as the princess,
بصفتها أميرة،
I'm sure she won't just give up so easily.
أنا متأكدة من أنها لن تستسلم بهذه السهولة.
She will probably complain to the emperor.
من المحتمل أنها ستشتكي للإمبراطور.
Are you worried that you might get me involved?
هل أنت قلق من أن تورطني في الأمر؟
With you protecting me,
بوجودك لحمايتي،
we will rise
سننهض
and fall together.
ويسقطان معاً.
Nanny, harder.
المربية، الأمر أصعب.
Wipe it off.
امسحه.
(Ugly) Sure.
(قبيح) بالتأكيد.
How dare a lowly courtesan
كيف تجرؤ عاهرة وضيعة؟
do such a thing to the princess?
هل يفعل المرء مثل هذا الشيء بالأميرة؟
She can't atone for her crime even if she dies 100 times.
لا يمكنها التكفير عن جريمتها حتى لو ماتت 100 مرة.
You...
أنت...
How dare you
كيف تجرؤ؟
trespass on the Mistress's room at night?
هل يجوز التعدي على غرفة السيدة ليلاً؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
The Governor orders me to remove all of Your Highness' belongings
يأمرني الحاكم بإزالة جميع ممتلكات سموكم
from the Governor's Residence.
من مقر إقامة الحاكم.
You...
أنت...
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
The emperor granted the marriage between the Governor and me.
وافق الإمبراطور على زواج الحاكم مني.
I'll see who dares do that!
سأرى من يجرؤ على فعل ذلك!
Your Highness received the royal family's grace
صاحب السمو حظوة العائلة المالكة
yet you can't endure others.
لكنك لا تستطيع تحمل الآخرين.
You've tried to harm the women of this residence multiple times
لقد حاولت إيذاء نساء هذا المنزل عدة مرات
and caused chaos at the Governor's Residence.
وتسبب ذلك في فوضى عارمة في مقر إقامة الحاكم.
The Governor asked me to inform Your Highness
طلب مني الحاكم إبلاغ سموكم
that the residence cannot afford to handle the princess.
أن مقر الإقامة لا يستطيع تحمل تكاليف رعاية الأميرة.
Move.
يتحرك.
- Yes.
- نعم.
Nanny!
مربية!
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
It's all right.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
I...
أنا...
I was rude.
كنت وقحاً.
I shouldn't argue with the princess.
لا ينبغي لي أن أجادل الأميرة.
With Her Highness' status as a royalty,
نظراً لمكانة صاحبة السمو كفرد من العائلة المالكة،
she is the most suitable candidate
إنها المرشحة الأنسب
to be Your Lordship's wife.
أن أكون زوجة سيادتكم.
When will you face me with your true identity?
متى ستواجهني بهويتك الحقيقية؟
I wonder what you mean?
أتساءل ماذا تقصد؟
You always seek revenge and use all possible tricks.
أنت تسعى دائماً للانتقام وتستخدم كل الحيل الممكنة.
You didn't even care about the Governor's Residence's Madam.
لم تكن تهتم حتى بسيدة مقر إقامة الحاكم.
Why do you pretend to be a concubine
لماذا تتظاهرين بأنكِ محظية؟
who only flatters me?
من الذي يمدحني فقط؟
Regardless of your identity,
بغض النظر عن هويتك،
you can tell me
يمكنك إخباري
any request you have.
أي طلب لديك.
As long as I can give it to you, I won't be stingy about it.
طالما أستطيع أن أعطيك إياه، فلن أكون بخيلاً بشأنه.
Can you give me anything?
هل يمكنك أن تعطيني أي شيء؟
Anything.
أي شئ.
Does it include your life?
هل يشمل ذلك حياتك؟
Come and take it anytime.
تعال وخذها في أي وقت.
Your Lordship, there's no need to flatter me.
يا صاحب السمو، لا داعي للمجاملة.
One day, you will believe
ستؤمن يوماً ما
that you won't have to
أنك لن تضطر إلى ذلك
put on a facade to protect yourself before me.
تظاهر بالقوة لحماية نفسك أمامي.
One day,
يوم واحد،
Your Lordship will also understand
سيتفهم سيادتكم ذلك أيضاً
that there is something
أن هناك شيئًا ما
that I can't afford to ask for
لا أستطيع تحمل تكلفة طلب ذلك
because I can't take it
لأنني لا أستطيع تحمل ذلك
and it isn't necessary.
وهذا ليس ضرورياً.
For the sake of the Governor's Residence,
من أجل مقر إقامة الحاكم،
Your Lordship should think of a way to resolve this.
ينبغي على سيادتكم التفكير في طريقة لحل هذه المشكلة.
♪So close yet we say nothing♪
قريبون جداً لكننا لا نقول شيئاً؟
♪Leaving one alone♪
ترك شخص ما بمفرده؟
♪Looking back upon heaven and earth♪
نظرة إلى الوراء على السماء والأرض
If the Governor's Residence
إذا كان مقر إقامة الحاكم
is going to sink,
ستغرق،
will you sink with me?
هل ستغرق معي؟
♪If a single thought could take us back to those years♪
لو أن فكرة واحدة قادرة على إعادتنا إلى تلك السنوات؟
♪Both like a dream and yet so real♪
???يشبه الحلم ولكنه حقيقي للغاية؟
♪One thought waits through wind and snow♪
فكرة واحدة تنتظر رغم الرياح والثلوج.
♪In memories pure and bright♪
في ذكريات نقية ومشرقة
There's no need to worry.
لا داعي للقلق.
♪Recalling a bygone chapter of our lives♪
???استذكار فصلٍ مضى من حياتنا؟
Even if the Governor's Residence sinks,
حتى لو غرق مقر إقامة الحاكم،
leaving you on the shore
سيتركك على الشاطئ
is still something I can manage to do.
لا يزال هذا شيئاً أستطيع القيام به.
♪To meet someday♪
نلتقي يوماً ما
♪Can we still hope♪
هل ما زال بإمكاننا أن نأمل؟
Pei Yu.
باي يو.
I grant Wan'er to you
أمنحكم وانير
because I want a good husband for her.
لأنني أريد لها زوجاً صالحاً.
In the end,
في النهاية،
she was already humiliated
لقد كانت تشعر بالإهانة بالفعل
by your concubine before both of you were married.
من قبل جاريتك قبل زواجكما.
Wan'er suffered a great grievance.
لقد عانى وانر من مظلمة كبيرة.
Even if I am not
حتى لو لم أكن كذلك
an emperor,
إمبراطور،
I must still stand up for her
لا يزال يتعين عليّ أن أدافع عنها.
as her father.
مثل والدها.
Your Majesty, regarding this...
جلالتكم، بخصوص هذا الأمر...
Someone,
شخص ما،
If a man wants to achieve something great,
إذا أراد الرجل أن يحقق شيئاً عظيماً،
he must not be troubled by a relationship.
يجب ألا يزعجه وجود علاقة عاطفية.
Offer this poisoned wine
قدّم هذا النبيذ المسموم
to your concubine.
إلى محظيتك.
Lord Pei,
اللورد باي،
are you feeling reluctant?
هل تشعر بالتردد؟
If you are,
إذا كنت كذلك،
I can
أنا استطيع
help you.
نساعدك.
She's just a concubine.
إنها مجرد جارية.
Why would I feel reluctant?
لماذا أشعر بالتردد؟
Your Lordship.
صاحب السعادة.
You got arrogant because I spoiled you and went against the princess.
لقد أصبحتَ متغطرسًا لأنني دللتك وخالفت أوامر الأميرة.
Drink the poisoned wine
اشرب النبيذ المسموم
yourself.
نفسك.
(End of Episode)
(نهاية الحلقة)
Can I say the Shen family case
هل لي أن أقول قضية عائلة شين؟
has absolutely nothing to do with me?
ليس لي أي علاقة على الإطلاق؟
What a great show.
يا له من عرض رائع.
♪Loneliness♪
الشعور بالوحدة
♪How do I cross it?♪
كيف أعبرها؟
♪Whom have I ever failed♪
من خذلتُ في حياتي؟
♪Incense burns through a few sticks♪
يحرق البخور بضع أعواد فقط؟
♪Can the rest of my life be redeemed?♪
هل يمكن إصلاح ما تبقى من حياتي؟
♪The flowing years pass through desolation♪
تمر السنين المتدفقة عبر الخراب.
♪Unwilling to forgive past mistakes♪
غير راغب في مسامحة أخطاء الماضي؟
♪Blaming myself for not protecting♪
ألوم نفسي لعدم حمايتي لنفسي.
♪Our vows as I should have♪
عهودنا كما ينبغي لي أن أفعل.
♪Sorrow♪
؟؟؟حزن؟؟؟
♪Counting it carefully♪
???أحصيها بعناية؟
♪Who stayed by my side through hardship♪
من بقي بجانبي في الشدائد؟
♪There will eventually be a pure land♪
سيأتي يومٌ تكون فيه أرضٌ طاهرة.
♪Where all karmic burden is cast away♪
حيث يتم التخلص من كل عبء كارمي
♪Not until worldly splendor fades♪
لن يحدث ذلك إلا بعد أن يزول بريق الدنيا.
♪Can one understand what cuts to the bone♪
هل يمكن للمرء أن يفهم ما الذي يقطع العظم؟
♪At dusk, with white hair♪
عند الغسق، بشعر أبيض؟
♪I still cannot fathom destiny♪
ما زلتُ عاجزاً عن فهم القدر.
♪After countless struggles across the waters♪
بعد صراعات لا حصر لها عبر المياه
♪At last the lotus heart awakens♪
أخيرًا يستيقظ قلب اللوتس!
♪Drifting across three lifetimes♪
???الانجراف عبر ثلاث حيوات؟
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
مجرد انتظار لنظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام؟
♪The distant mountains fade along the path home♪
تتلاشى الجبال البعيدة على طول الطريق المؤدي إلى المنزل.
♪I walk with you through morning bells and evening drums♪
أسير معك عبر أجراس الصباح وطبول المساء.
♪Our story lies in the mountains♪
قصتنا تكمن في الجبال
♪Like an ink-washed immortal painting♪
???مثل لوحة خالدة مغسولة بالحبر؟؟؟
♪Where blossoms fall♪
أين تتساقط الأزهار؟
♪I'm glad the fragrance in our hearts stays the same♪
أنا سعيد لأن العطر في قلوبنا يبقى كما هو.
♪Youth slips away♪
يتلاشى الشباب تدريجياً
♪Just to wait for your once-in-a-thousand-years glance♪
مجرد انتظار لنظرتك التي لا تتكرر إلا مرة كل ألف عام؟
♪Dreams wander back to the old road where we met♪
تعود الأحلام إلى الطريق القديم حيث التقينا.
♪Watching you gently play the zither♪
أشاهدك وأنت تعزف على آلة الزيثارة برفق.
♪Time rests upon the strings♪
يستقر الزمن على الأوتار.
♪Waiting for someone to brew a pot of tea♪
أنتظر أن يقوم أحدهم بتحضير إبريق شاي؟